A Guide to the Alfred E. Cohn papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA132
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1
  - Menge, Edward J.v.K. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Meyer, Margaret D. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Miller, James Alexander (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Miller, C. Phillip (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Miller, William S. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Minot, George R. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Mitchell, J.B. Jr. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Medical Society of the County of New York, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Medical Society of the County of New York, 1948-1951 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Medical Society of the County of New York, 1948-1949 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Medical Leaves, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Medical Preparedness, Committee on (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Medical Society of the County of New York, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Meleney, Frank L., 1943 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Mendez, Luis, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Menkin, Valy, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - The Menninger Foundation, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Merz, Charles (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Metcalf, K.D., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Meyer Anniversary Volume, Dr. Alfred, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Meyer, Marjorie, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Meyer, Dr. M.F. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Meyer, Ruth (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Meyer, K.F., 1940 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Meyerhof, Otto, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Metropolitan Life (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Mead, Kelson P., 1949 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Meyer, Eugene III, 1946-1947 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Merton, Robert K., 1943-1945 1949 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Meltzer, S.J. (Medical Brotherhood), 1916 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Mead, Johnson & Co., 1939 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Medallic Art Co., 1936 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Medico-Historical Press, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - McBee, Miss (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Mental Hygiene, New York City Committee on, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Meiss, Millard, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Melcher, Daniel, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Merz, Charles, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Meyers, Francis R., 1937 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Mebane, Jessie, 1923 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Meiklejohn, Alexander, 1926-1927 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Meier, Franz CM., 1926 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Meeker, Arthur, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Metcalfe, R.F., 1926 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Merrell, Margaret, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Magill, Peter (Art Bulletin), 1953 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1953-1954 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Michaelis, Leonor [re], 1945 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Miller, C. Phillip, 1940 1943 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Miller, James Alexander (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Miller, James Alexander, 1942 1944 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Miller-Rene Fülop (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Milner, B.C. Jr., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Millet, John A.P., 1940 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Miner, Eunice Thomas, 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Minot, George R., 1945 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Michie, H. Clay, 1926-1927 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Miller, C. Phillip, 1925-1927 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Miller, Reginald, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Miliband, R., 1949 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Miller, Benjamin F., 1950 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Milne, Alan, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Mirsky, Mrs. Alfred E., 1950 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Misch, Robert J., 1946 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Miller, Benj., 1936 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Miller, B.F., 1938 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Miller, C. Phillip, 1936-1938 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Miller, H.R., 1938 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Miller, James Alexander, 1936-1938 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Milliman, M.C., 1938 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Mitrany, David, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Mirsky, Alfred and Reba Paeff, 1929 1934-1936 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Mirsky, Alfred and Reba Paeff, 1940-1944 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Mirsky, Alfred and Reba Paeff, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Moore, Henry, 1936 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Moore, A.G., 1936 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Moorhead, John J., 1938 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Morokowitz, Marcia, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Morrison, A. Cressy, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Morrow, A.L., 1938 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Mosby, C.V. Co., 1938 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Moss, Mrs. Alfred S., 1939 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Mozo, Francisco Gnecco, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Mirsky, Alfred E., 1927 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Moody-Foster, E., 1924 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Morgan, Hugh, 1924 1927 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Morgan, J.L.R., 1923 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Morgan, T.H., 1927 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - "Will" [Physiological Laboratory, Cambridge], 1926 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Morgan, Hugh, 1941-1942 1944-1945 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Morris, Roger S., 1926 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Morison, R.A., 1922-1923 1925 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Mobitz, W. [re], 1926 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Moe, Henry Allen (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Mokotoff, Reuben (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Monnet, Jean, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Montgomery, Mrs. T.H. Jr., 1945 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Moody, Ellsworth (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Moore, Robert A. (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Moore, Robert F., 1940 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Morgan, Isabel M., 1942-1943 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Morison, R.A., 1943 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Morgan, Mrs. W.O.P., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Morley, Frank V. (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Morris, Dave Hennon, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Morse, Marie (Mrs. Charles), 1941-1942 1944 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Mosby, C.V. Co. (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Mosby, C.V. Co., 1941-1942 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Moss, W.L., 1943 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Mott, John L., 1942 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Mount Sinai Hospital, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Montefiore Hospital, 1925 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Moley, R., 1935 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Möller, E.H.H., 1929-1930 1934 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Morgan, Will, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Montague, J.F., 1929 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Montefiore Hospital, 1934-1935 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Moon, Virgil H., 1934 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Moore, Harry H., 1930 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Moore, Henry F., 1928 1932 1934-1936 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Morgan, Elisabeth, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Morgan, Mrs. W.O.P., 1931 1934 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Morgan, William, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Morison, R.A., 1935 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Morrow, Elizabeth C., 1934 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Moritz, Dr., 1929 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Moschowitz, Eli, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Mosenthal, Herman O., 1928 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Motor Policy (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Moe, Mr. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Moll, Albrecht, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Moore, Robert A., 1947 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Morgan, Mrs. W.O.P., 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Morley, Frank V. (Harcourt Brace and Co.), 1947-1948 1953 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Morse, Mrs. Charles A. Jr., 1948 1951-1952 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Morse, Charles A., 1953 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Moses, Robert, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Muhlberg, Wm., 1934 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Munly, W.C., 1933 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Murphy, T.F., 1932-1933 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Murphy, Mrs. James B., 1930 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Murphy, James B., 1929 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Murray, Henry A., Jr. ("Harry"), 1928-1935 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Murrow, Edward R., 1934 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Musser, J.H., 1929 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Muckenfuss, Dr. Ralph (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Muller, John, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Muller, George P., 1938 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Murray, H.A. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Murray, H.A., 1936-1937 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Murray, Josephine, 1936-1938 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Murrow, Edward R., 1936-1939 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Murrow, E.R. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Musser, J.H., 1938 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Munly, W.C., 1927 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Murrow, Edward R., 1942 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Mueller-Deham, Albert (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Mumford, Lewis, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Mumford, Edward P., 1943 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Musser, John H., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Murrow, Edward R. and Mrs., 1940-1945 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Murrow, Edward R. and Mrs., 1946-1953 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Murray, Henry A., Jr. and Mrs., 1924-1927 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Murray, Henry A., Jr. and Mrs., 1940-1949 1951-1953 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Muller, Jonas N., 1946 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Mumford, Lewis, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Murphy, George E., 1951 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Murphy, Mrs. George E., 1953 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Mutual Trust Life Insurance Co., 1947 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - New York Heart Association (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Nagel, Ernest (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - National Research Council, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Nelms, Mrs. A.C., 1953 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Netherlands Chamber of Commerce, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Newman, James R. and Mrs., 1948 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Nollen, E.B., 1946 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Northrop, John H., 1946 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Nation Associates (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Nelson, George, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - New Milford Times (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - The New Yorker, 1943 1945-1946 1952-1954 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - The New Yorker (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Nicholls, Elsie C., 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Newburger, Sylvia, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Niles, David K., 1942 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Nisnewitz, Samuel, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Nittis, Savas, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Norden, Ruth, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Nunan, Joseph D., Jr., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Nurnberg, Herman, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Nurses, Procurement and Assignment Service Committee, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Nyboer, Jan, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - New York Heart Association (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - New School for Social Research, Alvin Johnson, 1949-1950 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - New School for Social Research, Clara W. Mayer, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - New School for Social Research, Saul K. Padover, 1950-1951 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - New School for Social Research, Hans Simons, 1950-1952 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - New School for Social Research, Esther Levine, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - New School for Social Research, Benjamin Greenspan, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - New School for Social Research, Student lists (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - New School for Social Research, Manuscripts of lectures (Box 27, Folder 2-3)
  - New School for Social Research, Graduate Faculty, 1940-1945 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - New School for Social Research, Fund-raising, 1940-1944 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - W.W. Norton Co., 1951-1953 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - National Research Council Contract, 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Newman, George, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - The Nation and Athenaeum, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Nelson, Thomas and Sons, 1923-1925 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - New York Tuberculosis and Health Association (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Neumann, Charles, Correspondence, 1940-1946 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Neumann, Charles, Bibliography, manuscripts, reprints (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Notes (copied) (Box 27, Folder 11)
    Scope and Contents note
    [see Box 28, Folder 1 for continuation].
  - Notes (copied) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Notes (dictated) (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - "Health of the People May 2, 1 p. 1951"
    - "Transcript from tape recorder June, 32 pp. 1951"
  - Neuberger, Max [re], 1938 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - New York Public Library, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - National Student Federation of America (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Neill, James M., 1936 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Nemet, Mrs. Geza, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Neuhof, Mrs. Selian (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - New, Minnie, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Nicholls, Elsie C., 1938 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - de No, Lorente, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Nolan, Dr. Lewis (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Normandie House, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Norton, Allen, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Nylin, Gustav, 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Narcotic Department, Internal Revenue, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Nargizian, V.H. Inc., 1932 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Naumburg, Robert E., 1933 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Neal, Mrs. Benjamin B., 1935 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Neal, John W., 1927-1928 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Neal, Phil. H., 1935 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Necheles, H., 1926 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Nelson, Thomas & Sons, 1928 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Nomenclature of Disease, National Conference on, 1930-1931 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Nemet, G. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Neuhof, Mrs. S., 1935 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - New York Medical Week, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Neuhof, Dorothy, 1928-1929 1931 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Neuhof, Mrs. S., 1929 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - New, Minnie (Mrs. Harry), 1929 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - New York Central Railroad Co., 1928 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Nicoll, Matthias, 1930 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Nicholls, Elsie C., 1933 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Nichols, Stanley, 1931 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Niehues, Franz, 1931 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Niebyl, Karl Heinrich, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Norris, Charles, 1928 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Oliver, Jean, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - O'Loughlin, J.L.N., 1946 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Opie, Eugene L., 1946 1953 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Oppenheimer, B.S., 1946 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Osterhout, W.J.V., 1948 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Odencrantz, Louise, 1929 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Ogden, C.K., 1932 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - O'Hare, James D., 1929 1933 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Oler, C.B., 1935 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Olesen, Robert, 1932 1934 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Oppenheimer, B.S., 1933-1934 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Ortmayer, Marie, 1930 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Osgood, Robert B. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Osgood, Robert B., 1934 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Osterhout, W.J.V., 1931 1935 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - O'Brien, Daniel P., 1941 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Oliver, Jean, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Opie, Eugene L., 1940 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Oppenheimer, Bernard S. [re], 1941 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Oram, Harold L. and Mrs., 1942-1943 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Ornstein, Paul W., 1943 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Osterhout, W.J.V., 1942 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - O'Sullivan, Mary, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Ogburn, William F., 1938 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Oliver, Jean (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Opie, Eugene L., 1939 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Oppenheimer, B.S., 1936 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Opper, Lincoln, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Osgood, Dr. Robert B. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Osterhout, W.J.V., 1938 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Oxford University Press (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Ogata, D., 1927 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Olschki-Florence, Leo S., 1924-1925 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Oppenheimer, B.S., 1924-1927 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Osterhout, W.J.V., 1923 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Otto, Harold L., 1925-1927 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Obernauer, Thesa, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Oppenheimer, Albert [re], 1937 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Ornstein Memorial Volume", 1936 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Hess, Laing, Singer, Mr. Bean. Lambert", 1936-1938 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Ornstein Memorial Volume, [Singer, Bean, Hess], 1929 1931-1932 1936 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Ornstein Memorial Volume, [Laing, Hess, Bean, Stewart], 1926-1927 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Ornstein Memorial Volume, [autographs by George Sarton, Karl Sudhoff, Charles Singer, Henry Sigerist], 1928 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Ornstein Memorial Volume, [Singer, Hess, Bean], 1929 1931 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Pratt, Joseph H., 1924-1925 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Proskauer, Joseph M., 1923-1924 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Page, Irvine H., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Paley, William S., 1950 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Palmer, W.W., 1947-1948 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Palmer, W.W., 1948 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Park, Edwards A., 1951 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Parker, Philo W., 1947 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Parkinson, John, 1946 1948 1951 1953 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Pastore, John, 1947-1948 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Petrzelka, Charles, 1951-1952 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Pfeiffer, John E., 1946 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Physiological Congress, XVII International, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Papandreou, Const, and Andrew, 1947 1950 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Parelhoff, Albert D., 1948 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Paeff, Bashka, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Page, Irvine H., 1937-1938 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Page, John Randolph, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Palmer, W.W., 1939 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Pardee, H.E.B. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Parkinson, John, 1936 1939 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Patents, Memorandum on, 1932 November (Box 29, Folder 5)
    ("See letter to Mr. Bernard Flexner dated November 1932").
  - Patten, Bradley M., 1936-1938 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Peters, John P., 1937 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Packard, Francis R., 1928 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Paddock, Bruce W. and Mrs., 1933 1935 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Page, Irvine H., 1935 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Palmer, Walter W., 1929-1931 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Papamarku, P., 1929-1930 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Pappandreou, Const. A., 1928-1930 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Pardee, H.E.B. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Parker, Z. Rita, 1929 1931 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Parker, Raymond C., 1933 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Parkinson, John, 1929 1932-1933 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Parrott, James M., 1932 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Parsonnet, Aaron E., 1933 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Pasha, Mohamed Shahin, 1932 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Pearce, Louise, 1933 1935 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Pearce, Richard M., 1928-1929 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Pearcy, Frank, 1928 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Pearson, Karl (Box 29, Folder 7)
    See Kast, L.
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Agent. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    See Blachley, W.E.
  - Personnel Placement, 1926 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Perutz, Otto, 1932 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Peters, John P., 1931-1933 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Pforzheimer, Walter L., 1930 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Peabody, Francis W., 1923-1924 1926 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Peabody, Mrs. Francis W., 1927 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Pearce, Richard, 1923-1926 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Pearce, Richard-Einthoven visit, 1923-1924 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Palmer, Walter W., 1924 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Patents Bureau, United States, 1927 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Peabody Museum of Harvard University, 1926 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Pearce, Louise, 1923 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Pearl, Raymond F. [Pooler, B.F.], 1927 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Perry, E.D., 1925-1926 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Peters, John P., 1927 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Paley, Mrs. William S. (Dorothy), 1942-1944 1946-1947 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Page, Mrs. I.H., 1942 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Page, Irvine H., 1943 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Palmer, W.W., 1943 1945 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Paley, William S., 1941 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Papamarkou, Iris [re], 1945 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Pappenheimer, Alwin M., 1942 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Pardee, H.E.B., 1940 1943 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Park, Edwards A., 1941 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Parker, Philo W., 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Parkinson, John W., 1941 1944-1945 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Parker, Philo W. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    See Wilson, W.R.
  - Parkins, Wm. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    See Galati, C.
  - Parsons, G. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    See Herald-Tribune.
  - Patek, Arthur, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Paton, R. Townley, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Payne, E. George, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Patek Phillippe and Co., 1945 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Paul, John, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Pearce, Louise, 1941-1942 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Pearce, Ronald H., 1943 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Pepper, Claude, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Perry, Ralph Barton, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Petersen, Gustav H., 1941 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Pforzheimer, Carl H. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    See Irvington House.
  - Political and Economic Planning, 1939-1940 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Parcels (Fraser, Morris & Co.), 1941-1942 1950-1953 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Paul, John R., 1930 1932-1933 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Pearl, Raymond, 1928 1930 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Physicians, American Association of, 1934 1937 1939 1945-1955 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Physicians, American Association of, 1939 1941-1944 1954 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Piel, Gerard, 1948-1949 1952 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Pilvin, Harold, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Popper, Mrs; Kurt S., 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Pratt, Henry, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Pratt, Joseph H., 1952 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Precinct, 19th, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Prescott, Orville, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Pritchard, Edward, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Prokocimer, William, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Proskauer, Joseph M., 1946 1948 1950 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Psychosomatic Society, American, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - The Plaza Hotel, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Piel, Gerard, 1944 1948 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Pike, H.H. Jr. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    See Clark, G.
  - Plaut, Dr. Alfred (Box 30, Folder 4)
    See Ascheim, S.
  - Podell, David L., 1942 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Poletti, Charles, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Pope, Arthur Upham (Box 30, Folder 4)
    See Iranian Institute.
  - Popper, Lily, 1943-1944 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Poulson, Harper W. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    See International Student Service; Emergency Committee.
  - Pratt, Mrs. Eliot (Box 30, Folder 4)
    See Emergency Committee; I.S.S.
  - Pratt, Eliot, 1943 1945 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Pratt, George, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Pratt, Mrs. Eliot D., 1942 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Pratt, Joseph H., 1940-1941 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Proportional Representation (Box 30, Folder 4)
    See Hermans.
  - Pritchett, Ida W., 1927 1944 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Proskauer, Joseph, 1940-1943 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Proskauer, E.S. (Interscience Publishers), 1941 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Profile (Box 30, Folder 5)
    See Werner, M.R.
  - Pruitt, Ida, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Pullman Company, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Putnam, A.J., 1942 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Pictures, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Piel, Gerard, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Plehn, Dr. George J. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    See World's Fair.
  - Poletti, Charles, 1937 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Pool, Miss Naomi de Sola, 1938-1939 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Pope, Arthur Upham, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Posener, Karl (Box 30, Folder 6)
    See Lasker Foundation, Dr. Dick.
  - Poulson, Harper W. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    See I.S.S.
  - Pratt, Mrs. George D., Jr. [re] (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Pratt, Joseph H., 1938 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - The President (U.S., 1938 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Proskauer, Mrs. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    See Fortune, K.
  - Peabody, Mrs. Francis W., Francis G., Virginia, 1927-1928 1930 1932-1933 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Poll, Heinrich, 1931-1932 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Pollack, Herbert, 1933-1934 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Pollak, Miss M.H. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Pollitzer, Anita L., 1928 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Pond, C.F. (Cambridge University Press), 1929 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Pool, Eugene (Box 30, Folder 8)
    See Academy of Medicine, New York.
  - Porosowsky, Yetta (Box 30, Folder 8)
    See Hillman, Dr.
  - Potter, Flora W., 1931 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Poulard, Madame, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Pratt, Joseph H., 1932 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Priest, Walter, 1928 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Prodger, Samuel H., 1932 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Proskauer, Richard, 1926 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Proskauer, Joseph, 1928 1930-1933 1935 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Public Library, New York, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Pool, D. and Mrs. de Sola, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Portis, Milton M., 1924 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Pritchett, Ida W., undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Priestley (Box 30, Folder 9)
    Filed in Dr. Murray's folder.
  - Porosowska, Miss Yetta, 1931 1938 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Prichard, Edward F., Jr. ("Little Judge"), 1940 1944 (Box 30, Folder 9)